Okay, well, we now have all our sprites imported, so we have everything we need to start developing.
But before we start coding, I think it is best that we organize this a bit better so we know what is
going on.
Because if you could not tell, this is a bit of a mess and programming and well, most other things
in life, staying organized is key.
Now, I don't know if you've ever cooked in a very messy kitchen, but if you have, you will know the
struggle.
But luckily for you, this is going to be quick as there are only a few things that need to be neatened
up.
Firstly moving to our tree sprite here.
As you can see, this is just way too big and you may be thinking, well, I can just change the size
over here, but think about it, if you accidentally change it again, then you have to try and remember
how you had it, so it's always better to do it in the code editor.
So we can just bring out this go to block and then this set size block.
Well let's set the size to 30.
And then we can change the position.
Okay, let's just quickly hide the other sprite so we can see what's going on.
Okay, well, the size looks pretty good.
And then for the go to block, we don't even need to guess.
I can just drag it to where I want it, right at the corner here.
And then just copy these x y coordinates into my go to block.
Then lastly we can just put a when flag clicked on the script.
Then looking at the road lanes, you don't need to worry too much because we'll we'll be working with
this in the next lesson, but you can just drag it to the center for now.
Then for our obstacle course here, we also need to make it smaller and change the position so we can
just drag over this code again.
And while we are here, we can also drag it to our player car.
So for X we can just set it to zero.
Then y is fine.
The size can be a bit bigger and that should be good for now.
So lastly, looking at our car, let's move this to the center and change Y to be negative as we want
our car to on this side of the screen.
Okay, that's a bit too far down and our car is a bit small.
So again we can increase the size.
And then let's bring y up a bit.
As you can see this is a bit of trial and error thing.
But that looks about right.
Okay, well, there we have it.
Look how much better that looks.
We can actually see what's going on.
And now that we are properly organized, we can start cooking.
Or in our case, we can start programming.